So, in this lab,
Neste laboratório,
we tried out TF transform.
testamos o tf.Transform.
The reason that we're using TF transform is that it allows
O motivo para usarmos essa transformação é que ela permite
us to carry out preprocessing using Apache Beam,
configurar o pré-processamento no Apache Beam
but do the preprocessing in TensorFlow.
e fazê-lo no TensorFlow.
The idea is that we can create
A ideia é que podemos criar
preprocess datasets at scale during training and during evaluation.
conjuntos de dados de pré-processamento em escala
Then we can turn around and apply that preprocessing
Depois, podemos aplicar esse pré-processamento
on data that comes in for predictions,
em dados coletados nas previsões
and we can carry that out as part of a TensorFlow graph itself.
e como parte do próprio gráfico do TensorFlow.
So, let's look at how that's done.
Vamos ver como isso é feito.
The first thing is that TensorFlow transformer is not part of core TensorFlow,
Primeiro, o tf.Transform não faz parte do TensorFlow principal.
it is an open-source library,
É uma biblioteca de código aberto separada.
So, in order to do that,
Para isso,
I will go ahead and first install a specific version of transfer transform.
preciso instalar uma versão específica do tf.Transform.
So, we have to realize which version of TensorFlow we're
Precisamos ver qual versão do TensorFlow
using and the corresponding version of TensorFlow transform.
nós usamos e a versão correspondente do tf.Transform.
Now, when I recorded this video,
Quando gravei este vídeo,
I was using TensorFlow 1.5 and
eu estava usando o TensorFlow 1.5,
the corresponding version of TensorFlow transform for TensorFlow 1.5,
e o tf.Transform correspondente a essa versão
was transfer transform 0.5.
era a versão 0.5.
When you are doing it, it might be different.
Isso pode ser diferente para você.
The notebook, we will keep it up to date so that you will have the right version
Manteremos o bloco de notas atualizado para que você tenha a versão certa
corresponding to the right version of TensorFlow that's installed in the notebooks.
que corresponde à versão instalada nos blocos de notas.
So, in this case, I'm basically going to install TensorFlow transform
Neste caso, preciso instalar a versão 0.5 do tf.Transform
0.5 and I'm going to install the package Apache Beam-GCP.
e o pacote Apache Beam-GCP.
Again, just to make sure that we get everything correct.
Só para garantir que está tudo certo.
That already comes with Dataflow,
Ele já vem com o Dataflow,
we'll uninstall it because Apache Beam-GCP and Google Cloud Dataflow,
vamos desinstalar porque o Apache Beam-GCP e o Google Cloud Dataflow
they're essentially the same thing.
são essencialmente iguais.
But in this case,
Mas, neste caso,
we will just go with all of the open-source things.
usaremos só ferramentas de código aberto.
So, I'll go ahead and do a pip uninstall and a pip install.
Vou usar os comandos pip uninstall e pip install.
This is probably going to take a few minutes and once that's done,
Isso levará alguns minutos. Quando terminar,
we want to make sure that the notebook picks up the new pip packages.
precisamos garantir que o bloco de notas receba os novos pacotes pip.
The way you do this,
Para fazer isso,
is to go ahead and click Reset.
vamos clicar em "Reset".
So, we have to wait for this filled circle to become open again.
Precisamos esperar este círculo ficar vazio novamente.
That means that this particular cell has finished
Isso significa que a execução na célula terminou
executing and the appropriate pip installs are done.
e as instalações foram feitas.
So, let's go ahead and wait.
Vamos esperar.
this circle that was filled black is now open.
este círculo estava todo preto e agora está vazio.
That means that this cell has completed.
Isso significa que a célula foi concluída.
Actually, when you go ahead and look at the cell,
Quando você olha a célula,
you see that it has basically gone ahead and done a bunch of things.
pode ver que muitas coisas aconteceram.
you should see that it has uninstalled a bunch of things and installed a bunch of things.
você verá que muitas coisas foram desinstaladas e instaladas.
We do get the tents for transform 0.5.
Nós conseguimos instalar a versão 0.5.
So, but let's make sure.
Vamos ter certeza.
So, what we could do here is,
O que podemos fazer é,
first of all, we want to make sure that it gets picked up.
primeiro, garantir que os pacotes serão recebidos.
So, in order to do that,
Para fazer isso,
we will have to reset.
precisamos redefinir.
So, I'm clicking the Reset,
Então, eu clico em "Reset",
restarting the session, and at this point,
reinicio a sessão e, nesse momento,
the new pip packages will be picked up.
os novos pacotes pip serão recebidos.
We can go down,
Podemos descer
and we have a cell that basically does a pip freeze
e ver uma célula com pip freeze,
that tells you what's present on
que diz o que está presente
So, the vertical bar here is an R. So,
A barra vertical aqui é R.
let me do that and we should basically see that both
Quando clicamos, vemos que
TensorFlow transform and Apache Beam are installed,
o tf.Transform e o Apache Beam estão instalados,
TensorFlow itself is installed.
assim como o próprio TensorFlow.
In this case, we seemed to have like Tensor Board and Apache airflow,
Nesse caso, parece que temos o TensorBoard e o Apache AirFlow.
even though we don't need either of those.
Não precisamos de nenhum deles,
But they're there. So, we have that.
mas eles estão lá. Depois dessas etapas,
Now, we are ready to basically import TensorFlow,
estamos prontos para importar o TensorFlow
importance over transformers TFT,
com o comando import tensorflow_transform as tft.
and then make sure that you change
Lembre-se de alterar
your bucket in your project to reflect your Quick Labs project.
o intervalo do projeto para refletir o projeto do Qwiklabs.
I've already done this.
Eu já fiz isso.
So, I will go ahead and run that cell and makes sure that it can be picked up by Bash.
Vou executar a célula e garantir que ela seja detectada pelo Bash.
So, that's what a western environment does.
É isso que os.environ faz.
Make sure that my project and my compute region reflect this project and this region.
E preciso garantir que meu projeto e minha região correspondam a estes.
The next thing that we want to do,
Depois, o que precisamos fazer
is to basically get our data from BigQuery.
é coletar os dados do BigQuery.
But unlike the previous example,
Ao contrário do exemplo anterior,
we're not doing any more filtering on latitude,
não filtraremos mais a latitude,
longitude, et cetera, we will do that filtering in Apache Beam.
a longitude etc. Filtraremos no Apache Beam.
That way, we'll make sure if somebody gives us,
Assim, não há problema se alguém fornecer
during predictions, a bad input, we don't get host.
uma entrada inválida durante as previsões.
Okay? So, we'll basically just go ahead and pick up a few things.
Vamos coletar algumas coisas.
We'll do some preprocessing here to get the fare amount, et cetera.
Faremos parte do pré-processamento para ver o fare_amount etc.
But the query itself is much simpler than work as before.
Mas a consulta está muito mais fácil que antes
Because we'll carry out quite a bit of that preprocessing in Apache Beam.
porque grande parte do pré-processamento será no Apache Beam.
We'll go ahead and this time,
Dessa vez,
I will create a DataFrame valid.
eu criarei um DataFrame válido
Just to show you what happens.
para mostrar o que acontece.
I'm running the query,
Eu executo a consulta
I'm executing it, creating a Pandas DataFrame,
para criar um DataFrame do Pandas
and once I have the Pandas DataFrame,
e, quando tenho o DataFrame,
I'm calling head which shows me the first few lines.
uso o comando head para ver as primeiras linhas.
Then I'm calling describe,
Depois, o comando describe,
which will give me the mean and other statistics,
que mostra a média e outras estatísticas.
mean, standard deviation, and the quantiles of this particular DataFrame.
Média, desvio padrão e os quantis do DataFrame.
So, we have our DataFrame valid and we see that it basically has,
Temos nosso DataFrame válido e vemos que ele tem
no 11,181 columns of fare amount,
11.181 colunas de fare_amount,
hour of day, et cetera.
hourofday etc.
So, all of those and then it basically,
E, basicamente,
we now see that the query is correct.
podemos ver que a consulta está certa.
So, let's now use this query to create a machine learning dataset,
Vamos usá-la para criar um conjunto de dados de aprendizado de máquina,
this time using TF transform and using Dataflow.
dessa vez com tf.Transform e o Dataflow.
Unlike every Dataflow job that we've done so far,
Ao contrário dos jobs que executamos até agora,
we now need an extra package to be installed on the machines that run Dataflow.
precisamos que um pacote extra seja instalado nas máquinas com Dataflow.
The way we do this,
Para isso,
is to basically write a requirements.text.
escrevemos um requirements.txt.
So, remember that when we did a pip install, we basically said,
Quando usamos o comando pip install, escrevemos
pip install, TensorFlow transform 0.5.0.
pip install TensorFlow transform 0.5.0.
Well, that's exactly what we do here.
É isso que faremos aqui.
We go to, we write a requirements.text.
Escrevemos um arquivo requirements.txt.
In the requirements.text, we say that we want to install TensorFlow transform 0.5.0.
No arquivo, dizemos que queremos instalar o tf.Transform 0.5.0.
So, let's go ahead and write that.
Vamos escrever o arquivo.
Having written the requirements.text,
Depois de escrever,
we can now run our dataflow job passing in this requirements.text as a requirements file.
podemos executar o job do Dataflow com esse arquivo de requisitos.
So, this tells Dataflow that it needs to go through
Ele diz ao Dataflow que é preciso acessar
requirements.text and pip install all of the Python packages that we need.
o requirements.txt com pip install de todos os pacotes do Python necessários.
What is that we're doing in this job?
O que estamos fazendo nesse job?
In this job as with the previous jobs,
Assim como nos jobs anteriores,
we are going to be basically reading from BigQuery,
vamos ler o BigQuery
we are going to be creating records.
e criar registros.
But unlike the previous case,
Mas, ao contrário do caso anterior
we created CSV records, in this case,
em que criamos registros CSV, agora
we're going to create TensorFlow examples
criaremos exemplos do TensorFlow,
because they are more efficient. So, how does this work?
porque eles são mais eficientes. Como isso funciona?
We also need to create the training dataset in the evaluation dataset.
Também precisamos criar o conjunto de dados de treinamento e avaliação.
So, let's walk through this piece by piece.
Vamos ver esse processo passo a passo.
The first thing is to decide what kind of preprocessing we want to do.
Primeiro, decidimos o tipo de pré-processamento.
Okay. So, if you want to do two types of preprocessing,
Se você quiser usar dois tipos de pré-processamento,
one type of preprocessing,
o primeiro tipo
is that we want to check if
será verificar
the input row that we get is valid or not so that it is valid.
se a linha de entrada é válida ou não com is_valid.
Given a dictionary of inputs,
Em um dicionário de entradas,
what we get from BigQuery is going to be a dictionary and conveniently,
recebemos um dicionário do BigQuery e, convenientemente,
what we get during prediction from JSON is also going to be a dictionary.
o JSON também fornece um dicionário durante a previsão.
So, the same code is going to work both on
O mesmo código funcionará
We're going to get the inputs,
Vamos coletar as entradas.
the pickuplon, the dropofflon, the pickuplat,
Pickuplon, dropofflon, pickuplat,
the dropofflat, the hour of the day,
dropofflat, hourofday,
the day of the week, all of these things,
dayofweek, tudo isso.
we're going to try to get them.
Precisamos coletar tudo.
If any of them we're not able to get,
Se não for possível coletar algum valor,
we'll basically say it's not valid, right?
significa que ele não é válido, certo?
So, we're doing a try, except.
Então, usamos try/except.
So, we're going to basically do all of these things.
Precisamos fazer tudo isso.
If any of them throws an exception,
Se algum elemento retornar uma exceção,
we basically say this isn't valid.
ele não será válido.
Having gotten them, we then basically say it is valid if all of these conditions are met.
Depois de receber os valores,
If the fare amount is greater than 2.5,
Fare_amount é maior que 2,5,
and the pickup longitude is greater than negative 78, et cetera.
e pickup_longitude é maior que -78 etc.
So, all of these tests,
Fazemos todos esses testes.
if they all pass,
Se passarem,
then the inputs are valid.
as entradas são válidas.
Now we're going to take our data and we're going to basically do
Vamos usar os dados e fazer algumas coisas
things to make the neural network training better.
para melhorar o treinamento da rede neural.
So what are we going to do?
O que faremos?
We're going to basically take the inputs fair amount and pass it through unchanged.
Vamos enviar o fare_amount sem modificações.
If I could just say inputs fair amount or I could basically call some other function,
Eu poderia só dizer fare_amount ou chamar outra função.
like in this case, I'm calling TF identity, just pass it through.
Neste caso, estou usando tf.Identity para transferir.
What BigQuery gives us an integer like 1,2,3,4.
O BigQuery mostra um número inteiro como 1, 2, 3 ,4.
In the previous lab,
No laboratório anterior,
for the feature engineering lab,
de engenharia de atributos,
and we did this, what did we do?
o que fizemos com isso?
We essentially hard-coded in the vocabulary.
Essencialmente, incluímos o vocabulário no código.
In this case, we're basically going to tell TensorFlow Transform,
Neste caso, diremos ao TensorFlow Transform
go learn the vocabulary from the training dataset.
para aprender o vocabulário no conjunto de treinamento.
So now, we're not going to know necessarily know what this number means,
Agora, não sabemos necessariamente o que esse número significa,
but we know that whatever comes in during prediction,
mas sabemos que o que aparecer na previsão
will automatically get converted.
será convertido automaticamente.
So we're going to take the day of the week and we're going to convert that string that
Vamos converter a string de dayofweek
we get into an integer based on the vocabulary.
que recebemos em um número inteiro com base no vocabulário.
That's what the string to int does.
É isso que string_to_int faz.
The hour of day is already an integer,
Hourofday já é um número inteiro,
so we just pass it through unchanged.
então nós transferimos sem mudanças.
The pickup lawn is a floating point number.
Pickuplon é um ponto flutuante.
So we could also use it unchanged,
Também podemos usar sem modificações,
but we know that neural network training works a lot better,
mas sabemos que o treinamento da rede neural funciona melhor,
gradient descent works a lot better if our input values are small numbers,
o gradiente descendente funciona melhor com números menores,
if they're in the range for example, zero to one.
por exemplo, de 0 a 1.
So that's what we're asking TensorFlow Transform to do.
É isso que pedimos para o tf.Transform fazer.
TensorFlow Transform scale this value from zero to one.
O tf.Transform escalona esse valor de 0 a 1.
But remember, in order to scale it from zero to one,
Mas para fazer isso,
TensorFlow Transform needs to know what the minimum is and what the maximum is.
ele precisa saber os valores mínimo e máximo.
It will learn it from the dataset.
Ele aprenderá no conjunto de dados.
That's why we have the two phases.
Por isso temos duas fases.
We have the analyze phase and then we have the transform phase.
Temos a fase de análise e a de transformação.
So even though we're just writing that transform here scale zero to one,
Embora estejamos escrevendo scale_to_0_1 na transformação,
scale zero to one knows that in order to do this in the analyze phase,
ele sabe que, para fazer isso na fase de análise,
it has to find the min and the max.
é preciso encontrar o mínimo e o máximo.
So we do the same thing for all of these things,
Fazemos o mesmo para tudo isso.
and then we cast inputs that passengers to be a float,
Depois, usamos cast-inputs-passengers como um float
and then we basically take the inputs.passengers and we basically do at once like this.
e mudamos todos de uma vez, desta maneira.
So we basically get an equal number of ones and then cast it to be a string.
Conseguimos um número igual de uns e usamos cast para uma string.
So in this case, all of our keys are essentially the stringed one.
Nesse caso, nossas chaves são a string 1.
But this is just to give you an example of the fact
Mas isso é só um exemplo de que
that you can call arbitrary TensorFlow functions.
você pode chamar funções arbitrárias do TensorFlow.
Key thing is pre-processing is all TensorFlow functions.
O principal é que o pré-processamento é formado por funções do TensorFlow.
So having done that we also do engineering.
Depois, fazemos a engenharia.
Right? Again, TensorFlow functions, so in this case,
Novamente, funções do TensorFlow.
I'm taking the pickup lat, drop-off lat,
Neste caso, estou subtraindo pickuplat e dropofflat,
the lawn def that is computed and also scaling it.
que foram calculadas.
So again, we don't need to worry about what the difference,
Não precisamos nos preocupar em saber
what that scale is.
qual é a escala.
That's TensorFlow Transform's job to figure out
É o TensorFlow Transform que precisa descobrir
what the min and max are to scale it appropriately.
os valores mínimo e máximo para criar a escala.
Again, we then go ahead and take
Nós coletamos
these scaled values and then compute the Euclidean distance off the scaled values.
esses valores escalonados e calculamos a distância euclidiana deles.
We don't need to scale this again because we
Não precisamos escalonar novamente
then this square root will also be between zero and one.
então a raiz quadrada também estará entre 0 e 1.
So it's okay. It's all within that square.
Certo, está tudo nesse quadrado.
It will be 1.4 if both of them are one. But close enough.
Seria 1,4 se ambos forem 1, mas está perto o bastante.
They're small numbers, so we don't need to scale it, and at this point,
São números pequenos, então não precisamos escalonar.
So- but we still need to call the is valid method and the pre-process TFT method.
Mas ainda precisamos chamar os métodos is_valid e preprocess_tft.
We have to call both of these methods from within the beam transform.
Precisamos chamar esses métodos na transformação do Beam.
So how did we do that?
Como fazemos isso?
The way we do this is we first
Para isso, primeiro
set up the metadata for the raw data that we are going to be reading it.
configuramos os metadados para os dados brutos que leremos.
What's a raw data?
O que são dados brutos?
This is the data that comes from BigQuery.
São dados provenientes do BigQuery.
So we basically say that the day of the week and the key,
Dizemos que dayofweek e key são strings,
all of these things are floats,
são floats,
and we basically create a raw data schema which
e criamos um esquema de dados brutos
is essentially a dictionary that goes from
que é um dicionário que abrange
the name of the column to whether it's a string or it's a float or if it's an integer.
desde o nome da coluna até se o valor é uma string, float ou número inteiro.
Hour of day and passengers, they're both integers.
Hourofday e passengers são números inteiros.
This is in the raw data.
Esses são os dados brutos.
This is what comes out of BigQuery.
É isso que o BigQuery fornece.
So we take the raw data and we basically sell.
Nós usamos os dados brutos com o comando cell.
Let's go ahead and write the raw data metadata.
Vamos escrever os metadados brutos.
We write that out so that
Nós os escrevemos para que
the JSON input that comes in from the user will also be of this raw data metadata.
a entrada JSON recebida do usuário também seja desses metadados.
So we basically is going to be of this form and we want
Ela terá esse formato,
"Go ahead and read the data from BigQuery using the query that we've just
"Leia os dados do BigQuery com a consulta
So you see how it is valid method comes in.
Você pode ver como o método is_valid é usado.
It's being called as part of a beam filter.
Ele é chamado como parte de um filtro do Beam.
The beam filter is carried out with the rules that we specified in the is valid function.
O filtro é executado com as regras especificadas na função is_valid.
Then, we basically call,
Depois, chamamos
analyze, and transform dataset.
AnalyzeAndTransformDataset.
When we do that, we have to specify the transformation function.
Depois, precisamos especificar a função de transformação.
The transformation function is pre-process underscore TFT.
A função é preprocess_tft.
This is a one that does all the scaling, etc.
Ela faz todo o escalonamento etc.
So at this point, we basically get back the transform dataset and the transform function,
Agora, recebemos transformed_dataset e transform_fn.
and what we do is that we take the transform data and we write it out as TF records.
Pegamos transformed_data e escrevemos como TFRecords.
We write it out as TF records that are Gzipped,
Escrevemos como TFRecords no gz,
compressed to save space.
compactados para economizar espaço.
Then we do the same thing for the test data.
Depois, fazemos o mesmo com os dados de teste.
So in the training data,
Nos dados de treinamento,
I created the query at one,
eu criei a consulta com 1
and in the test data, I created query at two,
e, nos dados de teste, com 2.
and the way I set up my query was that depending on whether one or two was passed in,
A consulta é configurada dependendo de qual foi passado, 1 ou 2,
that was a phase.
nessa fase.
I either picked up the first few of the hash buckets or the last of the hash buckets.
Eu uso os primeiros intervalos de hash ou os últimos.
So that's how I'm getting my training dataset or evaluation dataset.
É assim que recebo meu conjunto de dados de treinamento ou avaliação.
So having done that,
Depois disso,
I now write out my transform
eu escrevo transformed_test_dataset
the test dataset and also write them out to the evaluation stuff and finally,
e também para os elementos de avaliação e, finalmente,
and this is very important,
e isso é muito importante,
we have to write out the metadata of the transformations.
precisamos escrever os metadados das transformações.
This is how all of the TF methods that we called,
É assim que todos os métodos TF chamados
they get stored in the graph.
são armazenados no gráfico.
So what this does is that it actually writes out a model.
Esse processo escreve um modelo.
A model actually isn't something that you train,
O modelo não é algo que você treina,
but it's a model that consists of TensorFlow operations that are going to
ele consiste em operações do TensorFlow
the TensorFlow Transform of TensorFlow functions into your normal model.
pelas funções do TensorFlow e cheguem ao seu modelo normal.
So with this, we are now ready and we can basically go
Com isso, está tudo pronto
If I set this to be true,
Se eu defino isso como true,
I would create a small dataset but I'm setting it to be false.
crio um conjunto de dados pequeno, mas vou usar false.
So this is actually going to run in
Isso será executado no Dataflow
get an error that says that the Dataflow API is not enabled,
que diz que a API Dataflow não está ativada,
go to the quick clubs project and enable the dataflow API and having done that,
acesse o projeto do Qwiklabs e ative a API.
Once that's done, then the training is very similar to what existed earlier.
Feito isso, o treinamento será parecido com o anterior.
But let's go and look at it.
Vamos dar uma olhada.
Let's look at what's actually different.
Vamos ver as diferenças.
So when we look at TensorFlow Transform under taxifare_tft,
Quando vemos o tf_Transform em taxifare_tft,
and in the model.pi, what is different?
e ver o que mudou nesse modelo.
So we basically get our input columns the same way as before.
Vemos as colunas de entrada da mesma forma que antes.
We're bucketizing, we're feature crossing,
Estamos intervalando e fazendo o cruzamento de atributos,
we are creating a white columns,
criando colunas brancas
we're creating a deep columns.
e colunas profundas.
All this is identical to the way we did our preprocessing.
Isso é idêntico ao pré-processamento.
Earlier, when we did it with DataFlow and we actually had
Antes, quando fizemos isso com o Dataflow,
In this case though,
Neste caso,
we don't need to do that, we don't have this ad engineered function.
não precisamos fazer isso, não temos essa função.
What that add engineered function was doing,
O que essa função estava fazendo,
TensorFlow Transform is now doing inherently as part of the graph.
o tf.Transform agora faz como parte do gráfico.
So what we're basically saying is,
Estamos dizendo o seguinte:
when somebody gives me a serving function,
Quando alguém oferece uma função de disponibilização,
I'm basically going to go ahead and read out of
eu preciso ler nessa função de transformação
take the raw data that comes in,
coletar os dados brutos recebidos,
so these are the raw data,
estes são os dados brutos,
and then basically apply everything that happens in TensorFlow Transform function,
e aplicar tudo que acontece na transform_fn,
all of these things that we did.
tudo isso que fizemos.
Essentially all of the code that we called in pre-process_tft,
Todo o código chamado em preprocess_tft
we're basically saying apply all of those to my features,
será aplicado aos meus atributos,
to my feature placeholder.
ao meu feature_placeholders.
So apply them to the feature placeholders,
Aplique-os a feature_placeholders,
get back the features,
receba os atributos,
and that is now the pair of things that we return.
e é isso que retornamos.
The feature placeholders is what the end-user gives us,
Feature_placeholders é o que o usuário final fornece,
the stuff that was in the JSON.
o que estava no JSON.
The features is a result of taking what was in the JSON and
Features é o resultado de coletar o que estava no JSON
applying all of that TensorFlow Transform transformation function,
e aplicar a função de transformação tf.Transform,
the transform function.
o transform_fn.
All of those operations do
Todas essas operações
the feature placeholders and that's essentially what gets returned.
para o feature_placeholders, que é retornado.
Now when we are reading the dataset, what do we have to do?
O que precisamos fazer ao ler o conjunto de dados?
When we're reading the dataset,
Na leitura,
we have to apply these transformations.
precisamos aplicar essas transformações.
Luckily though, we don't have to write that code ourselves because
Felizmente, não precisamos escrever o código,
an input function maker that you can basically go and say,
um criador de funções de entrada para o qual podemos dizer:
"Please build me a training input function that
"Crie uma função de entrada de treinamento
applies all of the stuff in the transform metadata.",
para aplicar tudo isso nos metadados de transformação".
and now go ahead and read it with Gzip and that's pretty much it.
Podemos ler com o Gzip e pronto.
It comes with the built training input function
Ele tem a função build_training_input
that knows how to read TensorFlow records.
que sabe como ler registros do TensorFlow.
So we don't have to write the whole normal code that we would write,
Não precisamos escrever todo o código
where would read a dataset,
para ler um conjunto de dados
and we'd apply a decode CSV.
e aplicar uma decodificação de CSV.
All of that stuff completely goes away.
Tudo isso desaparece.
We essentially just use
Essencialmente, só usamos
the build training input function to essentially do the job for us.
a função build_training_input para fazer o trabalho.
The train and evaluate is exactly the same as before.
O treinamento e a avaliação são exatamente como antes.
We create a train spec,
Criamos um train spec,
we create an eval spec,
um eval spec
and we pass in the estimator,
e passamos os dois para o Estimator.
The one difference was that because were you reading Gzip,
A única diferença é que, como você está lendo o Gzip,
we passed in a Gzip reader function,
passamos uma função de leitura do Gzip,
and the Gzip reader function is essentially a TF record reader that basically reads Gzip,
que é essencialmente um leitor de TFRecord que lê o Gzip.
and that's essentially it.
É basicamente isso.